Women's Building; Records apap292
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Programming, 1973-2000, Undated; 2; 4 cubic ft.
  - Women Make History, 1988; 1989 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 44)
  - Women Make History Walk, 1988; 1989 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 45)
  - Workshop/Program Registration, 1988 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 46)
  - Writing Workshops, 1988; 1989 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 47)
  - Art Against Violence, Capital Campaign, Grand Opening, 1989 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 48)
  - At the Heart of Healing, 1989 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 49)
  - Flyer Mechanics, 1989; 1997; 2000; 2001; Undated (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 50)
  - Girls Night Out Café, 1989-1992 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 51)
  - Grand Opening, 1989 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 52)
  - Grand Opening - Program, 1989 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 53)
  - Women Make History, 1989 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 54)
  - Auction, 1990 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 55)
  - Event Flyers, 1990-1991 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 56)
  - Networking Fair, 1990 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 57)
  - Program Forms, 1990 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 58)
  - Program Task Force Notes, 1990 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 59)
  - Reception Auction, 1990 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 60)
  - Supercupboard - Food Pantry Workshop, 1990 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 61)
  - Networking Fair, 1991 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 62)
  - Unfiled Programming, 1991; 1992 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 63)
  - Community Health Walk, 1992 (Box 2 (2-Programming), Folder 64)
  - Legal Clinic Concert, 1992 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 1)
  - Legal Clinic - Demographic Analysis, 1992 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 2)
  - Magda Enriquez, 1992 March (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 3)
  - Sites and Caterers for Events, 1992; 1998; Undated (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 4)
  - Women and Investing - Waddel + Reed, 1992 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 5)
  - Women's Networking Fair, 1992 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 6)
  - Women's Networking Fair, 1992 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 7)
  - Attendance/Event Report Blanks, ca. 1993 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 8)
  - Blues Women, 1993 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 9)
  - Blues Women, 1993 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 10)
  - Blues Women - Programs and Flyers, 1993 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 11)
  - Citizen Action: Human Rights, 1993 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 12)
  - Colloquium for Older Lesbians, 1993 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 13)
  - Colloquium for Older Lesbians, 1993 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 14)
  - Dismantling Racism Workbook, 1993 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 15)
  - Empowerment Project: Self-Defense, 1993 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 16)
  - International Women's Day, 1993; Undated (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 17)
  - Lavender Light, 1993 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 18)
  - Legal Clinic - Blank Forms, 1993 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 19)
  - Legal Clinics Disclaimers, 1992-1993 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 20)
  - Legal Clinic - Legal Disclaimer, 1993; 1994 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 21)
  - Legal Clinic - Mailing List, 1993 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 22)
  - Legal Project, 1993; 1994 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 23)
  - Legal Right Project Reception, 1993 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 24)
  - Phone Bank, 1993 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 25)
  - Potential Programs, 1993; 1994; 1996 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 26)
  - Women and Health Care, 1993; Undated (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 27)
  - Auction, 1994 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 28)
  - Auction: Celebrity List Updated, 1994-1995 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 29)
  - Auction Program, 1994 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 30)
  - Biographical Information: Burnstein, Karen, 1994 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 31)
  - Blues Women - Newsletter Calender, 1994 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 32)
  - Blues Women - Saffire Program, 1994 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 33)
  - Blues Women - Saffire Advertising, 1994 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 34)
  - Capital District Women's Bar Association - Demographic Analyisis, ca. 1994 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 35)
  - Community Walk, 1994 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 36)
  - Community Walk - UPS, 1994 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 37)
  - Donor Sheets, 1994 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 38)
  - Drum Festival, 1994 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 39)
  - Drum Festival - Press Packets, 1994 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 40)
  - Drum Festival - Press Work, 1994 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 41)
  - Drum Festival - Scholarship Sponsors, 1994 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 42)
  - Drumming - Holding Our Own Grant, 1994 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 43)
  - Films, 1994; 1995 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 44)
  - Hindu Goddess Series, 1994; 1995; Undated (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 45)
  - Legal Clinic - Comments Info, 1994; 1995 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 46)
  - Newsletter Writing Workshop, 1994 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 47)
  - Saffire: The Uppity Blueswomen Benefit - Patrons, Sponsors, 1994 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 48)
  - Washington Park Concert Series, 1994 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 49)
  - Women in Sports Program, 1994; 1995 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 50)
  - Art Exhibits, 1995 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 51)
  - Auction, 1995 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 52)
  - Auction Program, 1995 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 53)
  - Auction: Sponsors, Honored Guests, 1995 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 54)
  - Authors - Programs, 1995 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 55)
  - Community Brunch, 1995 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 56)
  - Community Walk - Freihoffers, 1995 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 57)
  - Craft Fair, 1995 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 58)
  - Dismantling Racism Committee, 1995; 1996 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 59)
  - Drum: Volunteer Coordinator, ca. 1995 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 60)
  - Drum Festival, 1995 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 61)
  - Drum Festival, 1995 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 62)
  - Drum Festival - Children's Drumming Flyer, 1995 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 63)
  - Drum Festival - Contracts, 1995 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 64)
  - Drum Festival - Expenses, 1995 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 65)
  - Drum Festival - Funding Packets, 1995 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 66)
  - Drum Festival - Funding Packets, 1995 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 67)
  - Drum Festival - Mailing List, 1995 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 68)
  - Drum Festival - Original Flyer, 1995 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 69)
  - Drum Festival - Resource List Original, 1995 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 70)
  - Drum Festival - Schedule and Program Material, 1995 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 71)
  - Drum Festival - Vendors, 1995 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 72)
  - Golf Tournament, 1995 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 73)
  - Golf Tournament - Registration Forms, 1995 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 74)
  - March 19th Call to Action, 1995 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 75)
  - Potential Programs, 1995; 1996 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 76)
  - Potential Programs, 1995; 1996 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 77)
  - Program Committee, 1995; 1996 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 78)
  - Tabeling Events, 1995; 1996 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 79)
  - Auction, 1996 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 80)
  - Auction, 1996 (Box 3 (2-Programming), Folder 81)
  - Auction - Friends of Auction Letter, 1996 (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 1)
  - Auction - Silent, 1996 (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 2)
  - Capital District Women's Bar Association, 1996 (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 3)
  - Capital District Women's Bar Association - Direct Mail, 1996 (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 4)
  - Capital District Women's Bar Association - Pro Bono Project Fundraiser, 1996 (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 5)
  - Co-Sponsored Events, 1996 (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 6)
  - Community Walk - Freihoffers, 1996 (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 7)
  - Community Walk originals, 1996 (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 8)
  - Drum Festival, 1996 (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 9)
  - Drum Festival, 1996 (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 10)
  - Drum Festival - Expenses, 1996 (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 11)
  - Drum Festival - Flyer and Program, 1996 (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 12)
  - Handivan, ca. 1996 (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 13)
  - Holding Our Own Grant Information, 1996 (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 14)
  - Legal Clinic - Intakes, 1996 (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 15)
  - Mortgages, Elizabeth Berg, HIV, 1996 (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 16)
  - Program Committee Meeting, 1996 (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 17)
  - Time Tunnel Summer Camp - Women's Building Sponsor, 1996 (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 18)
  - Auction, 1997 (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 19)
  - Auction, 1997 (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 20)
  - Auction - Certificates, ca. 1997 (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 21)
  - Auction - Program, 1997 (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 22)
  - Building Community/Programs, 1997; 1998; 2000 (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 23)
  - Capital District Women's Bar Association, 1997 (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 24)
  - Capital District Women's Bar Association, 1997 (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 25)
  - Capital District Women's Bar Association - Pro Bono Legal Project, 1997 (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 26)
  - Community Walk, 1997 (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 27)
  - Community Walk, 1997 (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 28)
  - Community Walk - Walker Letters, 1997 (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 29)
  - Community Walk - Pledges, 1997 (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 30)
  - Mother's Day Breakfast, 1997; 1998; Undated (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 31)
  - Picnic, 1997 (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 32)
  - Ubaka, 1997; 1998; Undated (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 33)
  - Auction, 1998 (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 34)
  - Capital District Women's Bar Assocation Directory, 1998 (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 35)
  - March on Washington Day, 1998 (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 36)
  - New York State Coalition Against Sexual Assault, 1998 (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 37)
  - Women's Building Community Walk, 1998 (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 38)
  - Women's Drumming Festival, 1998 (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 39)
  - Calendar, 1999 (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 40)
  - Jamie Anderson, 1999 (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 41)
  - Jamie Anderson Concert, 1999 (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 42)
  - Runaway Prevention Program, 1999 (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 43)
  - Co-Sponsorship Forms, Undated (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 44)
  - Community Walk - Instructions, Undated (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 45)
  - Community Walk - Membership Information, Undated (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 46)
  - Community Walk - Phone Scripts, Undated (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 47)
  - Community Walk - Pledge Letters, Undated (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 48)
  - Consciousness-Raising, Undated (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 49)
  - Effective Meetings, Undated (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 50)
  - Flyers, Undated (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 51)
  - For Signs and Posters, Undated (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 52)
  - Fundraising as Programs, Undated (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 53)
  - Legal Reception, Undated (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 54)
  - Materials to Distribute at Programs, Undated (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 55)
  - Movie Nights, Undated (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 56)
  - Program Task Force Meeting Agendas, Undated (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 57)
  - Resisters, Undated (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 58)
  - Thank You Notes, Undated (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 59)
  - Women and Sobriety Group, Undated (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 60)
  - Women Take Back the Night, Undated (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 61)
  - Barbara J. Wood and Katherine Maciol - Social Worker Programs, Undated (Box 4 (2-Programming), Folder 62)
- Resource File, 1954-2000, Undated; 3; 5 cubic ft.
  Alphabetical by subject
  The bulk of this series served as the Women's Building's information file on issues and problems facing the area's women. This is not to be confused with the Women's Building library which is not included in this collection, although indexes of the library are present in this series. The exact original contents of the Resource File are unknown as the original arrangement of the material was lost, but the series was gathered to include material in the collection that likely served primarily an informational purpose. This includes published material from other women's organizations, articles, pamphlets, newspaper clippings, referral and counseling information, and bibliographies or lists of further resources.
  - Abortion, 1972; 1977; 1978; Undated (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 1)
  - Abortion, 1973; 1976; 1977; 1978 (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 2)
  - Abortion, 1976; 1977; 1978 (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 3)
  - Abortion, 1976; 1977; 1979 (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 4)
  - Abortion, 1976; 1977; 1979; 1980; 1982 (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 5)
  - Abortion - News Stories, 1972; Undated (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 6)
  - Abrams, Robert (Statement on Child Abuse), 1984 (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 7)
  - Academic Essays, 1954; 1969; Undated (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 8)
  - Academic Essays, 1964; 1966; 1969; 1970; Undated (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 9)
  - Academic Essays, 1954; 1971; 1973; Undated (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 10)
  - Addiction Recovery Corporation, 1986 (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 11)
  - Adirondyke Newsletter, 1983; 1984 (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 12)
  - Affirmative Action, Undated (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 13)
  - Akwesashe Notes, 1978 (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 14)
  - Albany Area Women's Yellow Pages, Undated (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 15)
  - Albany Feminist Forum, 1982; 1983 (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 16)
  - Albany - NOW Newsletters, 1982; 1983; 1984 (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 17)
  - Albany Planned Parenthood, 1979 (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 18)
  - Albany Women Against Rape, Undated (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 19)
  - Alcoholism, Undated (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 20)
  - Alice Newsletter, 1982; 1983 (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 21)
  - Alliance Against Women's Oppression Discussion Papers, 1982; 1983 (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 22)
  - Amazon: A Midwest Journal for Women, 1976; 1977 (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 23)
  - Architecture, 1980's; 1989 (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 24)
  - Architecture, 1980's; 1989 (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 25)
  - Art Resources Open To Women (Schenectady), 1979 (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 26)
  - Articles, 1971; 1974; 1975; 1976 (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 27)
  - Articles Regarding Women, 1987; 1990-1994 (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 28)
  - Articles, 1988; 1990-1994 (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 29)
  - Assertiveness, 1976; 1979; Undated (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 30)
  - Assertiveness, 1977; Undated; 2000 (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 31)
  - Assertiveness, 1979; Undated (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 32)
  - Battered Women, Undated (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 33)
  - Battle Acts, 1974 (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 34)
  - Berkshire Women's News, 1984 (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 35)
  - Bibliographies, 1969; 1970; ca. 1973; 1978 (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 36)
  - Bibliography On Women And Militarism, Undated (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 37)
  - Bibliographies, 1971 (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 38)
  - Birth Control Handbook, 1970 (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 39)
  - Books, 1982; 1983; 1984; Undated (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 40)
  - Books, 1983; 1984 (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 41)
  - Brochures and Pamphlets From Gay Organizations, 1974; 1975 (Box 1 (3-Resource File), Folder 42)
  - Cambridge Women's Center Newsletters, 1989; 1990; 1991; 1992 (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 1)
  - Capital District Gay Community Center, 1982; 1983; Undated (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 2)
  - Career Planning, 1978; Undated (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 3)
  - Catalyst - Career and Education, 1975; 1976 (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 4)
  - Child Health Assessment Act of 1979 (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 5)
  - Chemical Dependency, Undated (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 6)
  - Classes, Undated (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 7)
  - Community, 1980; 2000 (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 8)
  - Consciousness Raising, Undated (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 9)
  - Conferences, Undated (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 10)
  - COSMEP: Committee of Small Magazine Publishes and Editors, 1976; 1977 (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 11)
  - Country Women, 1976 (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 12)
  - Credit Social Security, 1974; Undated (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 13)
  - The Daily Woman, 1977 (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 14)
  - Disability, 1975; 1977; Undated (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 15)
  - Domestic Violence, 1980 (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 16)
  - Domestic Violence Handbook, 1999 (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 17)
  - Educational Opportunities, 1977; 1976; 1979 (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 18)
  - Employment, 1973; 1974; 1975; Undated (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 19)
  - Employment, 1977 (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 20)
  - Employment Laws Affecting Women, 1973; 1974; 1975 (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 21)
  - ERA, 1970; Undated (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 22)
  - Every Woman's Council, Inc., 1981 (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 23)
  - Executive Women-Newsletters, 1974; 1975; 1976 (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 24)
  - Family Planning Advocates, 1983; 1984 (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 25)
  - Feminist Book Catalogs, 1974; 1976; 1977; Undated (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 26)
  - Feminist Bulletin(Westchester Co., NY), 1976; 1977 (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 27)
  - Feminist News, 2000 (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 28)
  - Films, 1975; 1979; Undated (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 29)
  - First New York State Women's Meeting, 1977 (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 30)
  - Flyers and Newsletters, 1999; 2000 (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 31)
  - Gay Information and Publications, 1975; 1979; Undated (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 32)
  - Grand Jury, 1975; 1976; Undated (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 33)
  - Grand Jury, Undated (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 34)
  - Green Light Project, Ithaca, NY, Undated (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 35)
  - HERA: A Philadelphia Women's Publication, 1976 (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 36)
  - Housing and Family Self Sufficiency, 2000 (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 37)
  - Housing Information, 1981; Undated (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 38)
  - The Hudson Valley Women's Times, ca. 1976 (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 39)
  - In These Times, 1978 (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 40)
  - Incest and Child Abuse, 1984 (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 41)
  - Job Bank, 1982-1983 (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 42)
  - Job Hunting/ Interviewing, 1980; 1983; Undated (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 43)
  - The Legal Status of Homemakers in N.Y. State, 1977 (Box 2 (3-Resource File), Folder 44)
  - The Legislative Gazette, 1999; 2000 (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 1)
  - Legislative, 1974; Undated (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 2)
  - Lesbian Information, 1970; 1979; Undated (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 3)
  - Lesbian Connection, 1982; 1983; 1984 (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 4)
  - Lesbianism and Sexuality, 1975; 1976; 1977; Undated (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 5)
  - Lesbianism and Sexuality, 1976; 1977; Undated (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 6)
  - Library Inventory, Undated (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 7)
  - Literature for Display, 1957-1973; Undated (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 8)
  - Local Rape Crisis Centers and Groups, 1977; Undated (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 9)
  - Majority Report, 1972; 1975; 1976 (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 10)
  - Majority Report, 1976; 1977 (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 11)
  - Majority Report, 1977; 1978; 1979 (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 12)
  - Tri-City Women's Center Marketing Research Project - Monica D. Robinson Marketing 380, 1975 (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 13)
  - Metropolitan Community Church, 1982; 1983 (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 14)
  - Millis, Carolyn Political Candidate, 1982 (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 15)
  - Joni Mitchell - Ladies of the Canyon, 1970 (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 16)
  - The National Lesbian Slideshow and Competition, Undated (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 17)
  - National Women's History Week, 1983 (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 18)
  - National Women's Organization (NOW) - New York and National, 1974; 1975; Undated (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 19)
  - National Women's Political Caucus, 1982 (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 20)
  - New Directions for Women, 1976; 1978 (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 21)
  - New York Radical Feminists, 1975; Undated (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 22)
  - New York State. A Horney General's Office, 1983 (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 23)
  - New York State Gay/Lesbian Conference - Newsletters, 1982; 1983 (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 24)
  - New York State. Higher Education Services Corporation, 1983; Undated (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 25)
  - New York State - National Abortion Rights Action League Newsletters, 1975; 1976; 1977 (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 26)
  - New York State Religious Coalition for Abortion Rights, 1975; Undated (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 27)
  - News Stories, 1972; 1975; 1977 (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 28)
  - The Next Step, 1987; Undated (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 29)
  - Nontraditional Jobs, 1977 (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 30)
  - Nuclear News, 1978; 1979; Undated (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 31)
  - Off Our Backs: A Women's News Journal, 1979 (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 32)
  - Pamphlets, 1975 (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 33)
  - Pamphlets - KNOW, Incorporation, 1968; 1970; Undated (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 34)
  - Pamphlets - New England Free Press, 1966; 1969; 1973 (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 35)
  - Pamphlets - Pathfinder Press, 1973; 1975 (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 36)
  - Pamphlets - U.S. Government Publications, 1973; 1977 (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 37)
  - Posted Information, 2000; Undated (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 38)
  - Pregnancy and Family Planning, 1980 (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 39)
  - Primetime(Independent Feminist Monthly), 1973 (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 40)
  - Prisons, 1975; Undated (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 41)
  - Process and Structure - Criticism, Self-Criticism, Conscious-raising, Facilitating, 1974; Undated (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 42)
  - Rape, Undated (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 43)
  - Rape-Crisis Programs, Undated (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 44)
  - Resolutions Adopted by Delegates to the National Women's Conference, Houston, 1977 November (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 45)
  - Sexism and Education, 1971; 1972; 1976 (Box 3 (3-Resource File), Folder 46)
  - Sexual Harassment, 1980-1981; Undated (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 1)
  - Sexual Harassment Workshop, 1980; 1981; Undated (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 2)
  - Sexuality, 1972; 1975; 1976; 1984; Undated (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 3)
  - Sister: Los Angeles Feminist News, 1979 (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 4)
  - Sister - New Haven Women's Liberation Newsletters, 1974; 1975; 1976 (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 5)
  - Sisters United, 1981; 1982; 1983; 1986 (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 6)
  - Sojourners - Kingston, New York, 1983; Undated (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 7)
  - South End Scene, 1978 (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 8)